One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Germa 66 once conquered the North Blue by force.
‫قامت جيرما 66 ذات مرة بإخضاع الأزرق الشمالي بالقوة‬
The six Vinsmokes at the top will be riddled with bullets tomorrow.
‫أهم 6 شخصيات في عائلة فينسموك سيتم رديهم بالرصاص غدًا‬
The wedding ceremony will be...
‫ستتحول أرضية القاعة...‬
dyed red with blood.
‫إلى اللون الأحمر‬
But even when you're dying,
‫ولكن حتى في لحظة موتكم‬
please try not to get your blood everywhere. And don't scream out, either.
‫لا تدعوا دماءكم تتناثر في كل مكان وتطلبوا الرحمة بجزع‬
You have to be careful.
‫حريّ بكم الحذر‬
If the wedding cake gets splattered with blood, Mama will be furious,
‫ستغضب ماما إن تلطخت كعكة الزفاف بالدماء‬
and she'll destroy the building.
‫وستدمر المكان على بكرة أبيه‬
This is a .36 caliber Walker percussion pistol.
‫مسدس كولت ووكر ذو عيار 36‬
It fires bullets called candy jackets.
‫«رصاصه معروف أيضًا باسم «كاندي جاكيت‬
They're powerful enough to pierce through armored soldiers.
‫إنه مصمم خصيصًا لاختراق الجنود المدرعين حتى وإن كانوا يرتدون ستر واقية‬
But you've already witnessed its power firsthand, right?
‫أنتِ تعرفين قوتها المباشرة، صحيح؟‬
These bullets will be able to penetrate all of your metal-enhanced bodies.
‫سوف تخترق أجسادكم المعززة بالمعادن‬
I can't wait for tomorrow!
‫لكم أترقب رؤية هذا‬
I want to see Sanji's face when I, the one he trusts, points a gun at his head.
‫كيف ستكون نظرة سانجي الذي وثق بي وأنا أوجه هذا السلاح نحوه؟‬
I can't wait to see that!
‫كم أترقب ذلك‬
The Jelly
‫الهلامي نترو‬
The Carpet
‫البساط رابيان‬
He truly believes that you love him!
‫إنه يصدّق أنكِ واقعة بغرامه‬
It'll be something to see.
‫يا له من أمر جميل لمشاهدته‬
What will his face look like?
‫كيف سيبدو؟‬
Let's see... Maybe it'll look like this?
‫فلنرَ... ربما هكذا؟‬
That's perfect!
‫سيكون هذا رائعًا‬
You're so funny!
‫سيكون الأفضل‬
Or maybe like this?
‫أو هكذا؟‬
P-Pudding-chan...
‫بـ-بودينغ-تشان‬
What's wrong? You aren't paying attention.
‫ما الأمر؟ أنتِ لا تنظرين إليّ‬
We're talking about your brother.
‫نحن نتحدث عن أخيك‬
She's right. Why don't you listen?
‫إنها محقة، لِمَ لا تنظرين؟‬
Listen!
‫استمعي لها‬
Do you want to know how he proposed to me?
‫أتريدين معرفة كيف تقدم لي؟‬
Oh! It was perfect!
‫كان ذلك الأفضل‬
When he pulled off the face pack, he looked terrible.
‫حينما نزع قناع الوجه، بدا في هيئة شنيعة‬
But I was waiting for that exact moment.
‫ولكنني كنت أنتظر تلك اللحظة بالضبط‬
By showing tears right there,
‫بدأت أذرف الدموع أمامه‬
I won his heart.
‫وأصبح قلبه من نصيبي‬
I won't let your marriage with me be hell!
‫لن أدع زواجك بي يكون جحيمًا لك أيضًا‬
Seriously, men are dumb.
‫يا لحماقة الرجال حقًّا‬
Then that idiot pulled me into his arms right then and there,
‫ذلك الأحمق قام بجذبي واحتضاني بشدة‬
and said in a quiet whisper,
‫وهمس لي بصعوبة‬
"You're my salvation. Let's get married."
‫«أنتِ هي خلاصي، لنتزوج»‬
"Let's get married."
‫«لنتزوج»‬
Stop it! I can't breathe!
‫توقفي، لا يمكنني التنفس‬
Hey.
‫اسمعي‬
That's such a pathetic proposal, don't you think?!
‫إنه طلب يد مثير للشفقة، أليس كذلك؟‬
Oh, it was so funny!
‫كم هذا مضحك‬
Who in the world would marry a failure like him?!
‫من تلك التي ستتزوج من فاشل مثله؟‬
Couldn't it at least have been a proper prince?
‫على الأقل، اجلبوا لي أميرًا نبيلًا حقيقيًّا‬
Sanji!
‫سانجي‬
Germa's Failure
‫فشل جيرما‬
Are you still trying to get up?
‫أما زلت تحاول المقاومة؟‬
Treasure Repository
‫مستودع الكنوز‬
Yes, I am.
‫أجل‬
Why? Why do you want to keep standing, Soul King?
‫لماذا؟ لِمَ لا تزال تقاوم يا ملك السول؟‬
Is it because of the stone, Soul King?
‫أهو من أجل الحجر يا ملك السول؟‬
Is that more important to you than rescuing Sanji?
‫أتفضّل الحصول على نسخة من النصوص الحجرية أكثر من استعادة سانجي؟‬
Yes.
‫أجل‬
Sanji-san is a kind man.
‫سانجي-سان رجل طيب القلب‬
That's why I figured he'd never come back.
‫لهذا السبب توقعت أنه لن يعود أبدًا‬
I don't know what kind of trap you set for him...
‫لا أعرف كيف قمتم بإغواءه‬
but he's an extremely kind man,
‫ولكنه طيب القلب حقًّا‬
so once he's made up his mind to sacrifice himself for someone, he will not change his mind!
‫بمجرد أن يقرر التضحية بنفسه من أجل شخص آخر، فهيهات أن يتراجع‬
And our captain, at the same time, is someone who always trusts his own beliefs when he acts!
‫وفي المقابل، قبطاننا يثق بنفسه ويتبع حدسه‬
That's why those two young men will decide what happens here!
‫الأمر عائد لذانك اليافعان لتحديد ما هو أفضل‬
I see!
‫هكذا إذًا‬
So you have nothing better to do than come for the stone?
‫أنت تسعى لذلك الحجر لأنك لا تمتلك شيئًا لفعله إذًا؟‬
No, I am doing it so that if, in the worst-case scenario, Sanji-san does not return with us,
‫كلا، في أسوأ الأحوال، إن قرر سانجي-سان عدم العودة‬
he will not blame himself for bringing us here!
‫لا أريده أن يلوم نفسه‬
I want him to know that this rescue mission was still beneficial!
‫أريده أن يعلم أننا كسبنا غنيمة عظيمة من مهمة الإنقاذ هذه‬
So I must get it! The lode poneglyph!
‫لذا سأحصل على بونغليف الطريق‬
Your worst-case scenario is too tame.
‫فكرتك عن أسوأ الأحوال سخيفة للغاية‬
Sanji not returning? Is that really the worst that could happen?
‫عدم عودة سانجي تعتبره أسوأ الأحوال؟‬
I don't think it is.
‫لا أظن ذلك‬
Do you think nobody's gonna die?
‫أتظن أنه لن يموت أحد؟‬
Maybe all of you will die!
‫قد تموتون جميعًا‬
What kind of fool draws up plans with the expectation of death, young lady?
‫من الأحمق الذي يعتبر موته جزءًا من الخطة أيتها الآنسة الصغيرة؟‬
Mirro-world
‫عالم المرايا‬
St... St... Stop!
‫توقفي‬
Okay! Tickle, tickle, tickle!
‫حسنًا، دغدغة، دغدغة‬
Tell us already!
‫أخبرينا بسرعة‬
Carrot's special tickle, tickle, tickle!
‫حيلة كاروت الخاصة، دغدغة، دغدغة‬
Stop!
‫توقفي‬
Stop tickling me!
‫توقفي عن دغدغتي‬
Just say it! If you don't, she'll tickle you forever!
‫هيا أخبرينا، لن تكف عن دغدغتك إن لم تتحدثي‬
I'll say it! I'll say it!
‫سأخبركم، سأخبركم‬
Okay, Carrot, stop.
‫عظيم، توقفي يا كاروت‬
Okay.
‫حاضر‬
I'll make you pay for this!
‫سأجعلكِ تدفعين ثمن هذا‬
Answer our question. Which mirror leads to the castle?
‫أجيبينا بسرعة، أي مرآة تقودنا للقصر؟‬
I don't remember every single mirror!
‫لا أذكر ممر أي مرآة‬
That's not the right answer!
‫تلك ليست الإجابة الصحيحة‬
You have to ask the mirrors!
‫ما أعنيه أنّ بإمكانكم سؤال المرايا‬
Huh? The mirrors?
‫نسأل المرايا؟‬
Ask?
‫نسألهم؟‬
That's right! The mirrors all know what they're reflecting!
‫هذا صحيح، كل مرآة تعرف انعكاسها‬
Mirror, mirror!
‫أيتها المرايا‬
Which one of you is a mirror to the castle?!
‫أي واحدة منكم تقودنا للقصر؟‬
I am!
‫أنا‬
It's me.
‫وأنا‬
Me too.
‫وأنا أيضًا‬
They answered!
‫لقد أجابونا‬
Here! Me too!
‫هنا، أنا أيضًا‬
Me too!
‫وأنا كذلك‬
I'm the mirror in Mistress Galette's closet.
‫أنا مرآة في خزانة غاليت-ساما‬
I'm a hand mirror in a guest room on the second floor.
‫أنا مرآة محمولة في غرفة الضيوف في الطابق الثاني‬
I'm a mirror in the ladies' room on the fourth floor.
‫أنا مرآة غرفة النساء في الطابق الرابع‬
Do any of you currently reflect Luffy, Nami, Brook, Pedro, or Sanji?
‫أي منكم تعكس لوفي أو نامي أو بروك أو بيدرو أو سانجي؟‬
We're looking for them!
‫نحن نبحث عنهم‬
Who?
‫من؟‬
What do they look like?
‫كيف يبدون؟‬
Prince Sanji passed by earlier.
‫لقد مرّ سانجي-ساما قبل قليل‬
Oh, yeah. They don't know what they look like.
‫هذا صحيح، إنهم لا يعرفون أشكالهم‬
Count on me, Chobro! I'm good at drawing!
‫دع الأمر لي يا تشونيكي، إنني جيدة في الرسم‬
What? Drawing?
‫الرسم؟‬
Uh-huh!
‫أجل‬
You're so unfortunate to have such a dumb brother.
‫يا لحظكِ العاثر بوجود أخ أحمق مثله‬
Yeah, you really are!
‫محقة، محقة‬
If we leave her like this, she'll be dead before the morning.
‫ستموت قبل بزوغ الفجر إن تركناها على هذا الحال‬
We can't let that happen. That'll ruin our whole plan.
‫ستفسد خطتنا بالكامل إن سمحنا بحدوث ذلك‬
We need her to live until tomorrow.
‫نحن بحاجتها حية إلى يوم الغد‬
Now, Big Sister.
‫والآن يا أختاه‬
It'll give us trouble if you die like this.
‫سنقع في مأزق إن هلكتِ‬
And it'll give us trouble if you reveal my ungraceful nature,
‫وسنقع في مأزق إن كشفتِ عن هويتي الحقيقية التي رأيتها‬
What are you...?
‫ما الذي تفعلينه...‬
Stay calm. It won't take long.
‫ابقي ساكنة، لن يستغرق الأمر وقتًا طويلًا‬
This is the power of the Memo-Memo Fruit.
‫هذه هي قدرة فاكهة الذاكرة‬
Everyone has a roll of film in their head that records memories.
‫كل شخص لديه شريط فيلم في عقله يحفظ الذكريات‬
You have scary experiences, sad memories,
‫لديكِ تجارب مخيفة وذكريات حزينة‬
and things that you want to forget, don't you?
‫وأخرى تريدين نسيانها، صحيح؟‬
I'm impressed with Germa 66.
‫كما هو متوقع من جيرما 66‬
You were shot in the leg, but you still made it that far.
‫لقد أُصبتِ في ساقك، ورغم ذلك تمكنتِ من الهرب بعيدًا‬
You're uselessly tough!
‫قوة لا جدوى منها‬
She's right!
‫محقة‬
Now, I'll paste a memory strip
‫أنا أقوم الآن بلصق بضع الذكريات‬
from one of the soldiers who was shot by a stray bullet here and...
‫من جندي أصيب برصاصة عشوائية هنا ومن ثم...‬
Edit!
‫إيديت‬ ‫تعديل‬
All done!
‫انتهينا‬
Your most recent memories involving me have been cut.
‫ذكرياتكِ الأخيرة عني قد قُصّت‬
Let's have a joyous wedding tomorrow.
‫لنحظ بحفل زواج سعيد غدًا‬
Call the soldiers to escort her to the medical room.
‫استدعوا الجنود لحملها إلى غرفة العناية الطبية‬
Okay.
‫حاضر‬
Prisoner Library
‫مكتبة السجن‬
Stop! No!
‫توقف، كلا‬
Seriously, stop it, Luffy! You're scaring me! That's enough!
‫توقف حقًّا يا لوفي، أنت تخيفني، هذا يكفي‬
Stop it! Your arms really will be torn apart!
‫توقف، ستتمزق ذراعاك حقًّا‬
I don't care! I gotta tell Sanji about Pudding!
‫لا يهمني، يجب أن أخبر سانجي حالًا بحقيقة بودينغ‬
That rat!
‫تلك الحقيرة‬
No! I said don't do it! Luffy!
‫كلا، توقف يا لوفي‬
He's so reckless. Hey, girl.
‫يا له من متهور‬
What?! I'm busy now!
‫ماذا تريد؟ أنا في ورطة الآن‬
Mama ordered me to get Lola's whereabouts out of you during the night.
‫أمرتني ماما أن أحصل على موقع لولا منك في غضون المساء‬
So just tell me now.
‫لذا أخبريني بموقعها‬
No! I'm not going to sell out my friend!
‫كلا، لن أخون صديقتي‬
Okay, then. I'm gonna torture you.
‫سأعذبكِ إذًا‬
No! Don't say that so casually!
‫كلا، لا تقل هذا بكل برود‬
Alright, I'm gonna shoot you with a crossbow once every five seconds,
‫سأطلق عليكِ باستخدام القوس مرة كل خمس ثواني‬
so just tell me whenever you're ready.
‫لذا تحدثي متى ما أردتِ‬
What? What do you mean?
‫ما الذي تقوله؟‬
Don't do that... It'll kill me!
‫توقف، هذا سيتسبب بقتلي‬
Then just tell me.
‫هيا تحدثي إذًا‬
Screw you, wart head! I won't let you do that!
‫هذا يكفي يا رأس البثور، لن أسمح لك بفعل هذا‬
It's gonna be okay, Nami! I'll rip my arms off in the next five seconds!
‫لا بأس يا نامي، سأمزق ذراعي خلال خمس ثواني‬
No! I don't want either of those to happen!
‫كلا، لا أريد منك فعل هذا أيضًا‬
Don't be a baby!
‫لا تكوني أنانية‬
Hey! Is anybody here?!
‫أثمة أحد هنا؟‬
Oh! Whoa! Whoa! I thought you weren't allowed to enter the castle now!
‫مهلًا، مهلًا، اعتقدت أنه غير مخوّل لك دخول القصر الآن‬
Don't be so hardheaded. There is chaos all over this castle.
‫ثمة قتال في كل مكان، كفّ عن العناد‬
Sorry to do this, Opera...
‫أعتذر يا أوبرا‬
Five Thousand Tile...
‫غوسين مايغاوارا‬ ‫خمسة آلاف لكمة‬
Fist!
‫سيكن‬ ‫قرميدة‬
Sorry. Why don't you sleep for a while?
‫المعذرة، ما رأيك أن تأخذ غفوة قصيرة؟‬
Jinbe!
‫جينبي‬
Oh, Luffy! Nami!
‫لوفي، نامي‬
Why are you here?!
‫لِمَ أنت هنا؟‬
I heard you got caught. I'm glad that you're okay.
‫سمعت أنهم قبضوا عليكما، أنا سعيد أنكما بخير‬
We can talk later.
‫لنؤجل الحديث لاحقًا‬
But first, don't you want to get out of there?
‫أولًا، أتريدان الخروج؟‬
We do!
‫أجل‬
Whole Cake Chateau
‫قصر الكعكة الكاملة‬
Medical Room
‫الغرفة الطبية‬
She was bleeding badly, but the wound has already started healing.
‫بدأت تتماثل في الشفاء بعد أن كانت تنزف بشدة‬
What incredibly resilient and regenerative skin.
‫لديها بشرة صلبة بنحوٍ لا يُصدق وقدرة تعافٍ مذهلة‬
This is the true power of Germa's modified humans.
‫هكذا هي طبيعة البشر المعدلين لجيرما إذًا‬
If she stays in bed for the night, she should be able to attend the tea party tomorrow.
‫ستتعافى وتتمكن من حضور حفلة الشاي إذا لازمت السرير‬
Guard her for the rest of the night.
‫لازِمها طوال الليل‬
Don't forget to tell the Vinsmokes about this.
‫لا تنسى إخبار عائلة فينسموك‬
I'm sure they're worried about her.
‫لا بدّ أنهم قلقون عليها الآن‬
Yes, sir.
‫حاضر‬
Anyway, I'll be in the medical office on the fourth floor.
‫سأذهب للمركز الصحي الموجود في الطابق الرابع‬
I don't have time to sleep with the amount of wounded people that are in the castle right now.
‫لا يمكنني النوم، ثمة الكثير من المصابين في القلعة هذه الليلة‬
Thank you for your service. Take care.
‫شكرًا على عملك، رافقتك السلامة‬
Where am I?
‫أين أنا؟‬
Sanji!
‫سانجي‬
I hurt my leg...
‫ساقي مصابة‬
Do you remember how that happened?
‫أتذكرين كيف حدث ذلك؟‬
I was walking around the castle,
‫حينما كنت في جولة حول القصر‬
and then I ran across soldiers who were going after intruders...
‫صادفت بعض الجنود الذين كانوا يسعون خلف دخلاء‬
and I got attacked, I suppose?
‫وأظنني تعرضت لهذه الإصابة حينها؟‬
That doesn't make sense, does it? Of course not.
‫ألا يبدو الأمر مريبًا؟‬
Your memories were replaced.
‫لقد تم التلاعب بذاكرتك‬
I'll tell you what really happened.
‫سأخبرك بحقيقة ما حدث لكِ‬
Prisoner Library
‫مكتبة السجناء‬
Books can be destroyed by fire.
‫النار هي الحل الأمثل للتخلص من الكتب‬
Are you gonna burn the cage? Is that a good idea?
‫هل ستحرق الزنزانة؟ أواثق من هذا؟‬
Yes, but only if you two can get out of there before burning up.
‫سيكون جيدًا إن تمكنتما من الخروج قبل أن تلتهمكما ألسنة اللهب‬
Alright. Do it!
‫فهمت، افعلها‬
That quick?!
‫بهذه السرعة؟‬
No, I'm still not ready!
‫كلا، ما زلت غير مستعدة‬
We're really gonna burn!
‫سنحترق حقًّا‬
Burn it up already!
‫احترق بسرعة‬
Alright!
‫عظيم‬
Ouch!
‫حار‬
Hurry up! Luffy! Nami!
‫بسرعة يا لوفي ونامي‬
We got out!
‫لقد نجونا‬
I feel like I've been through something like this before...
‫أشعر أنني مررت بمثل هذا الموقف مسبقًا‬
Thanks to you, I didn't have to rip my arms apart!
‫لم أضطر لقطع ذراعي بفضلك، شكرًا لك‬
Come to think of it, we met each other...
‫بالمناسبة، لقد التقينا أول مرة‬
in a prison like this.
‫في سجن كهذا‬
Look! These people were all inside that book.
‫انظرا، لقد كانوا محبوسين في نفس الكتاب مثلكما‬
The imagination and span of the World of Books is infinite.
‫عالم الكتب يتخطى حدود خيالكما، هو عالم لا نهاية له‬
Big Mom has many powerful followers just like Mont d'Or.
‫بيغ مام لديها الكثير من الأتباع الأقوياء مثل مونت دور‬
Thank you, Jinbe! But why are you here?
‫شكرًا لك يا جينبي، ولكن ما سبب وجودك هنا؟‬
My Sun Pirates are also affiliated with Big Mom.
‫طاقم قراصنة الشمس الذي أقوده تابع لبيغ مام أيضًا‬
Oh, but...
‫ولكن...‬
that means this is...
‫إذًا هذا يعني...‬
Yes, this is a rebellion. There's no turning back now!
‫أجل، إنه تمرد، لم يعد بإمكاني التراجع‬
What? Is that okay?
‫ألا بأس بذلك؟‬
On Fishman Island, you said that you had other obligations.
‫لقد قلت أنه ما تزال لديك بعض المسؤوليات في جزيرة البرمائيين‬
I just took care of them.
‫تخليت عنها للتو‬
Someone heard screams from the Prisoner Library!
‫أحد الحرس سمع جلبة صادرة من مكتبة السجن‬
What's going on?!
‫ماذا يحدث؟‬
Ugh, they've already noticed!
‫لقد اكتشفوا الأمر‬
They're indeed quick.
‫إنهم سريعون كما توقعت‬
First, we have to hide in a place where they can't find us.
‫علينا أولًا الاختباء في مكان لا يمكنهم العثور علينا فيه‬
– Yeah. – Let's go, then!
‫هذا صحيح‬
All of a sudden... I feel hungry.
‫أشعر بالجوع فجأة‬
You're hungry at a time like this?
‫هل تشعر بالجوع في ظروف حاسمة كهذه؟‬
Luffy expends three times the energy of a normal person when he does something.
‫لوفي يستنزف طاقته أكثر بثلاثة أضعاف من الأشخاص العاديين حتى في قيامه بأبسط الأمور‬
It's okay. I'm not saying that I wanna eat something.
‫لا بأس، لم أقل أنني سآكل شيئًا‬
Your stomach is growling.
‫قرقرة معدتك واضحة‬
Never mind!
‫لا بأس‬
I won't eat anything other than what you cook!
‫لن أتناول شيئًا سوى ما تطهوه‬
Even if I get hungry or spears rain down on me,
‫حتى إن أصابني الجوع، أو اخترقتني الرماح‬
I'll stay right here and wait for you!
‫سأظلّ هنا بانتظارك‬
Anyway, Jinbe, thank you!
‫على أي حال، شكرًا لك يا جينبي‬
I actually...
‫في الواقع...‬
was proposed to by Sanji-san.
‫سانجي-سان قد طلب يدي‬
I'm not going to marry him, because...
‫لن أتزوجه، لأن...‬
he's an idiot that played right into my hands by falling for me...
‫ذلك الأحمق فريسة سهلة وقع في مكيدتي‬
and because he's going to be shot in the middle of the ceremony...
‫وسأرديه قتيلًا بيدي خلال مراسم الزفاف‬
Things can't get any worse!
‫الوضع سيئ للغاية‬
We were all fooled! Sanji too! I gotta let him know!
‫لقد خُدعنا نحن وسانجي، يجب أن أخبره‬
Take care of Nami, Jinbe!
‫اعتنِ بنامي يا جينبي‬
Luffy, wait! There are tons of tough enemies in the castle!
‫مهلًا يا لوفي، ثمة الكثير من الأعداء الأقوياء في القصر‬
And you're not fully recovered! Don't you remember what happened this morning?!
‫كما أنك لم تتعافى كليًّا، ألا تذكر ما حصل هذا الصباح؟‬
I'm not gonna be defeated this time!
‫لن أُهزم هذه المرة‬
Medical Room
‫الغرفة الطبية‬
Do you believe me?
‫أتصدقيني؟‬
Of course, I do. I know you wouldn't lie to me.
‫بالطبع، أعرف أنك لن تكذب عليّ‬
But I didn't realize Pudding's true character was this heinous.
‫ولكن لم أتوقع أن تكون شخصية بودينغ الحقيقية بهذا المكر‬
I wasn't completely sure.
‫لم أكن واثقة كليًّا‬
But I thought she seemed a little too perfect,
‫ولكن مثاليتها كانت مبالغة‬
so I was spying on her myself.
‫لذا كنت أتجسس عليها بمفردي‬
If she wasn't planning to marry me from the start, and if the plan was to kill us all along,
‫إن لم تكن تخطط للزواج بي من البداية وكان هدفها قتلنا جميعًا‬
then the promise I was given that Luffy and the others would be safe...
‫إذًا وعدهم بالعفو عن لوفي وبقية رفاقي إذا تزوجتها ليس سوى كذبة‬
I thought I could sacrifice myself, and everything would be fine!
‫حسبتُ أنّ كل شيء سيكون بخير إن ضحيت بنفسي‬
But that was nothing but false hope! How could I have been so naive?
‫ولكن كل هذا كان محض خيال، كيف لي أن أكون بهذه السذاجة؟‬
Our father may be smart, but even he was careless in this situation.
‫والدنا رجل ذكي، ولكنه خُدع في هذا المشروع‬
He's dealing with an emperor. He should've been more careful.
‫إنه يتعامل مع أحد الأباطرة، كان عليه أن يكون أكثر حذرًا‬
But this is a good situation, in my opinion.
‫ولكنها فرصة مثالية لنا‬
I believe that Germa should be destroyed.
‫أظن أنّ على جيرما أن تسقط‬
I'll just pretend I know nothing,
‫لنتظاهر أننا لا نعلم شيئًا‬
and let Big Mom's plan be carried out...
‫وندع بيغ مام تمضي في مكيدتها‬
What are you talking about? If you go to the tea party, they'll kill you too, Reiju!
‫ما الذي تقولينه؟‬
Oh, are you worried about me?
‫عجبًا، هل أنت قلق عليّ؟‬
This is the problem with old memories.
‫يبدو أنّ ذلك بسبب ذكرى رحيلك عنّا...‬
You don't need to think that you're indebted to me for helping you that one time.
‫إياك أن تظن أنك مدين لي بسبب مساعدتي لك سابقًا‬
Leave this island with the Straw Hats, Sanji.
‫غادر الجزيرة مع طاقمك يا سانجي‬
Huh?! I can't do that! If I do that, what will happen to the Baratie?
‫ماذا؟ لا يمكنني فعل هذا حتى إن استطعت، ماذا سيحل بباراتي؟‬
You can worry about that after you've escaped.
‫فكر بشأن ذلك بعد هربك‬
If you stay here, everybody will die.
‫سنموت جميعًا إن بقيت هنا‬
Sanji, you can't die. For our mother's sake!
‫يجب ألّا تموت يا سانجي، من أجل أمنية والدتنا‬
What do you mean?
‫ماذا تقصدين؟‬
I have a memory that I will never forget.
‫ثمة ذكرى لا يمكنني نسيانها‬
What are you talking about?
‫ما الذي تتحدثين عنه؟‬
Mother and Father had a big fight.
‫كان هناك شجار بين أمي وأبي‬
It happened when I was a child.
‫كنتُ مجرد طفلة‬
I always wondered why our sweet mother was so angry.
‫لذا كنت مستغربة من مدى غضب والدتنا الحنونة‬
But it made sense much later.
‫ولكن اتضح كل شيء لاحقًّا‬
When our mother was pregnant with you four,
‫كانت والدتنا حبلى في ذلك الوقت‬
she was strongly against turning you into emotionless machines.
‫كانت معارضة بشدة أمر تحويلكم أنتم الأربعة إلى آلات قتل عديمة المشاعر‬
– Are you serious?! – Of course I am!
‫هل أنت جاد؟‬
How can you want to do such a horrible thing?
‫كيف لك أن تفعل شيئًا شنيعًا كهذا؟‬
The operating room is ready.
‫العملية الجراحية جاهزة‬
Don't do this! They're my children, too!
‫لا تفعل هذا، إنهم أطفالي‬
If you get rid of their emotions, they won't be human anymore!
‫لن يكونوا بشرًا إن كانوا دون مشاعر‬
I want them to be monsters. Winning wars is all that matters.
‫أريدهم أن يكونوا وحوشًا، كل ما يهمني هو الانتصار في الحروب‬
The reestablishment of the Vinsmoke family that once conquered the North Blue.
‫أريد إعادة مجد عائلة فينسموك الذين حكموا الأزرق الشمالي بالقوة في الماضي‬
Accomplishing that goal... requires strength.
‫القوة هي الشيء الوحيد القادرة على تحقيق ذلك الحلم‬
I'll give my children the greatest power possible!
‫سأهب أولادي القوة المطلقة‬
What are you...? No! Let go of me!
‫ماذا تفعلون؟ كلا، دعوني‬
Dear! Don't do it! They're my children!
‫لا تفعل هذا يا عزيزي، إنهم أطفالي‬
No!
‫كلا‬
Then they performed the surgery.
‫بعد ذلك، أُجريت العملية الجراحية‬
But our mother took a powerful drug to try and foil our father's plan.
‫ولكن والدتنا تعاطت عقارًا بعد العملية لإحباط خطة والدنا‬
Hey, what have you done, Sora?
‫ما الذي فعلته يا سورا؟‬
This drug was strong enough to affect the manipulated hereditary elements.
‫تعاطت عقارًا قويًّا يمكنه التأثير على عناصر السلالة التي تأثرت بالجراحة‬
But her actions weren't enough.
‫ولكنها لم تنل ما تتمنى‬
They soon found superhuman abnormalities in our brothers' bodies.
‫لقد وجدوا في أجساد إخوتي قدرات خارقة تفوق قدرات البشر‬
I can't believe it!
‫مذهل‬
The surgery was a success.
‫لقد نجحت العملية الجراحية‬
Great!
‫جيد‬
Don't worry! Their genetic blueprints won't be affected by some drug.
‫لا تقلق، جيناتهم الأساسية لن تتأثر بعقار أو سواه‬
Let's play!
‫لنلعب‬
But it's strange. Only Prince Sanji is...
‫ولكن هذا غريب، سانجي-ساما الوحيد...‬
That can't be right. Let's watch over his growth.
‫ثمة شيء خاطئ، لنراقب نموه‬
Are you hungry? Hold on.
‫هل أنتما جائعين؟ لحظة‬
Here.
‫تفضلا‬
Is it good?
‫أهو لذيذ؟‬
Prince Sanji is feeding birds!
‫سانجي-ساما يُطعم الطيور‬
He mustn't have those kinds of emotions!
‫لا يجب أن يكون لديه مثل هذه التصرفات‬
Sora!
‫سورا‬
As you grew up, you kept acting human.
‫لقد واصلت النمو كشخص يتحلى بصفات البشر‬
Meanwhile, our mother grew weaker and weaker,
‫وبالمقابل، ازدادت حالة والدتنا سوءًا بسبب أعراض العقار الجانبية‬
Then... she died because of me?!
‫أهذا يعني أنها ماتت بسببي؟‬
Don't think like that!
‫لا تفكر هكذا‬
Mother...
‫أمي‬
Reiju! Come here!
‫ريجو، تعالي إليّ‬
How is your father doing?
‫كيف حال والدك؟‬
All he does is train us. He never plays with us.
‫إنه لا يلعب معنا، وكل ما يفعله هو تدريبنا‬
He's just happy that Ichiji, Niji, and Yonji seem to be fine soldiers.
‫إنه سعيد أنّ إيتشيجي ونيجي ويونجي يبدون جنود أقوياء‬
I see.
‫فهمت‬
What is that?
‫ما هذا؟‬
Sanji cooked it for me!
‫لقد طبخه سانجي لي‬
Sanji did?
‫سانجي؟‬
Can you guess what Sanji told me today?
‫هل تعرفين ما قاله لي سانجي اليوم؟‬
He said, "Get well soon."
‫«قال: «تحسّني بسرعة‬
He's the sweetest boy in the world!
‫إنه ألطف طفل في العالم‬
What are you doing here?
‫ماذا تفعل هنا؟‬
Father...
‫أبي...‬
This compassion to lay flowers for the dead is useless to you!
‫أن تأخذ بك الشفقة لجلب الزهور لضريح ميت هو أمر لا يجدر أن يصدر من ابني‬
Stop crying!
‫توقف عن البكاء‬
Coward!
‫أيها الجبان‬
Crybaby!
‫طفل بكّاء‬
Let's go.
‫لنذهب‬
You too. Come on.
‫تعالي معنا أنتِ أيضًا‬
Yes, sir.
‫حاضرة‬
But our father's beliefs were the total opposite of our mother's,
‫ولكن معتقدات والدنا كانت معاكسة لمعتقدات والدتنا تمامًا‬
and he never accepted you for who you were.
‫ولم يتقبل هويتك إطلاقًا‬
He blamed you for everything that happened, and mistreated you accordingly.
‫ألقى باللوم عليك حيال كل شيء حدث وقسى عليك‬
Never cook again!
‫لا تطبخ أبدًا بعد الآن‬
What are you doing?! Fight back!
‫ما الذي تفعله؟ قاتلني‬
Sanji is a worthless failure!
‫سانجي فاشل عديم الجدوى‬
Failure! Failure!
‫فاشل، فاشل‬
Run!
‫اركض‬
Don't look back!
‫لا تنظر للخلف‬
Even though our mother is no longer with us, her grace is still there inside of you.
‫ما زالت أمنية والدتنا بداخلك رغم عدم تواجدها معنا‬
There's no way that you're a failure.
‫أنت لست فاشل على الإطلاق‬
Our mother protected her child at the risk of her own life,
‫خاطرت والدتنا بحياتها في سبيل حماية ابنها‬
and he was born with the spark of humanity.
‫وقد وُلد وهو يحمل مشاعر وأحاسيس بشرية‬
That child is you, Sanji.
‫ذلك الطفل هو أنت يا سانجي‬
That's why you're kinder than anyone else!
‫لهذا السبب أنت طيب القلب أكثر من أي أحد آخر‬
Look for Straw Hat!
‫اعثروا على قبعة القش‬
Which way did he go?!
‫أي طريق سلك؟‬
He escaped from the underground Prisoner Library and passed through the first floor already!
‫لقد خرج من سجن المكتبة الواقع تحت الأرض، وعبر الطابق الأول سلفًا‬
Everyone, go to the second floor!
‫ليتجه الجميع إلى الطابق الثاني‬
Yes, sir!
‫حاضر‬
Sanji!
‫سانجي‬
Whole Cake Chateau 2nd Floor
‫الطابق الثاني في قصر الكعكة الكاملة‬
Treasure Repository Entryway
‫أمام بوابة مستودع الكنوز‬
What?! Another problem?
‫ماذا؟ مشكلة أخرى؟‬
Yes, ma'am. Boss Jinbe is in the castle and...
‫أجل، قام الزعيم جينبي داخل القصر...‬
He's not rebelling, is he?
‫أيعقل أنه تمرد علينا؟‬
Alright. Send this message to all soldiers.
‫حسنًا، أخبر الجنود بما سأقوله لك‬
Okay.
‫حاضر‬
Tomorrow's plan is Mama's long-awaited dream.
‫مهمة الغد هي حلم طال انتظاره لماما‬
Y-Yes.
‫نعم‬
What will happen if we fail?
‫ماذا سيحدث إن أخفقنا؟‬
In the worst-case scenario, what'll happen?
‫في أسوأ الأحوال، ماذا سيحدث؟‬
I-I don't want to think about it!
‫لـ-لا أريد التفكير بذلك حتى‬
Me neither.
‫ولا أنا‬
If we bring any more problems to Mama in her current mood,
‫إن ضايقنا مزاج ماما بأي مشكلة إضافية‬
it'll affect tomorrow's mission.
‫سيؤثر ذلك على مهمة الغد‬
You're right!
‫صحيح‬
Then what shall we do?
‫ما العمل إذًا؟‬
A-Are you... telling me to lie–
‫أيعقل أنكِ ترمين بكلامك أن أكذب على...‬
If you lie to Mama, you'll be executed.
‫ستهلك إن كذبت على ماما‬
F-Forgive me!
‫سـ-سامحيني‬
If there isn't a problem, we don't need to tell her anything.
‫لا حاجة لإخبارها بشيء إن لم تكن هناك أي مشكلة‬
Don't you agree?
‫صحيح؟‬
Y-Yes, I agree!
‫هـ-هذا صحيح‬
We're on the fourth floor.
‫نحن في الطابق الرابع‬
Block all the paths up to this floor!
‫اغلقوا كل الممرات المؤدية إلى هذا الطابق‬
Handle everything on the lower levels.
‫ليصبح كل شيء في قبضتكم في كل الطوابق الدنيا الأخرى‬
And get the situation under control immediately!
‫انهوا كل المشاكل حالًا‬
Yes, ma'am. Understood!
‫مفهوم‬
In that case, it's easier to kill them than to capture them!
‫في هذه الحالة، قتلهم سيكون أكثر ضمانًا من القبض عليهم‬
That's fine. You have my permission!
‫لا يهمني، أنا أسمح لك بفعل ذلك‬
Yes, ma'am!
‫حاضر‬
Where's Sanji?!
‫أين سانجي؟‬
I'm asking where he is!
‫أخبرني أين هو؟‬
Why are you still thinking?
‫لِمَ لا تزال غارقًا في تفكيرك؟‬
You already have your answer.
‫لقد سمعت الإجابة‬
Abandon Germa and run away, Sanji.
‫تخلى عن جيرما واهرب يا سانجي‬
Germa clings to glories from the past and stands for nothing but destruction.
‫إنّ جريما مجرد مدمرين يسعون لاستعادة مجد ماضيهم‬
The world doesn't need us.
‫لا حاجة للعالم بنا‬
All Big Mom wants is our advanced technology.
‫كل ما تريده بيغ مام هو التكنولوجيا العلمية الخاصة بنا‬
I doubt she has any interest in the life of your mentor.
‫لا أظنها مهتمة بسلب حياة منقذك‬
Father and our brothers are the ones who are threatening to take that seafaring restaurant hostage,
‫والدك وإخوتك الذين يتخذون المطعم البحري كرهينة لديهم‬
and they'll be dead tomorrow.
‫سيموتون غدًا‬
It's exactly what we deserve, since we're nothing but a band of murderers.
‫نحن نستحق الموت لأننا قتلة‬
My grudge is with them, but why do you have to die too?!
‫لا تسيئي فهمي، أنا أكرهم أيضًا ولكن لِمَ يتوجب عليكِ الموت معهم؟‬
I still have my emotions,
‫ما زالت هناك بعض المشاعر البشرية بداخلي‬
but I'm still a modified being that cannot disobey Father's orders.
‫لكنني متواطئة معهم، فقد عُدّلت على عدم عصيان أوامر أبي‬
My hands are stained with blood, too.
‫إنني شريكة بالجرائم أيضًا‬
I deserve death.
‫أنا أستحق الموت‬
I forgot to mention it, but those bracelets...
‫نسيت أن أخبرك بشأن هذه الأساور‬
They won't explode on you. I swapped them out for ordinary ones.
‫لن ينفجروا لأنني بدلتهم بأساور عادية‬
So what else is keeping you here?
‫أهنالك سبب آخر يرغمك على البقاء هنا؟‬
Get your act together, Sanji!
‫استيقظ من غفلتك يا سانجي‬
Outta my way!
‫تنحوا عن طريقي‬
Think about what's important to you!
‫ضع نصب عينيك أهم ما لديك‬
What's important to me?
‫أهم ما لدي؟‬
Stop, Straw Hat!
‫أوقفوا قبعة القش‬
Join my pirate crew!
‫انضم لطاقمي‬
Be the cook on my pirate ship!
‫كن طاهي قراصنتي‬
Where are you?!
‫أين أنت؟‬
You're a good cook, so let's be pirates together!
‫أنت طاهٍ بارع، لتكن قرصانًا معي‬
You'll never be able to meet...
‫أوفياء مثلهم‬
good friends...
‫لن يتكرروا...‬
like them again!
‫في حياتك أبدًا‬
Outta my way!
‫ابتعدوا عن طريقي‬
Sanji!
‫سانجي‬